{
    "subject": "resource/Corrosion_of_Conformity",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Corrosion of Conformity is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8782463073730469,
            "question": "What country is Corrosion of Conformity's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7658693194389343,
            "question": "Corrosion of Conformity's hometown is in which continent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7528422474861145,
            "question": "Where is Corrosion of Conformity from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246130108833313,
            "question": "Where were Corrosion of Conformity formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6460585594177246,
            "question": "Is Corrosion of Conformity an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5694335699081421,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Corrosion of Conformity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5209195613861084,
            "question": "Corrosion of Conformity's home country is the United States. What genre of music are they known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21753522753715515,
            "question": "What is the musical origin of Corrosion of Conformity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019371598958969116,
            "question": "Is the United States known for its music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.018752167001366615,
            "question": "Can you name a band from the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Corrosion of Conformity is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9175_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the United States known for its music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9175_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the musical origin of Corrosion of Conformity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9175_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Corrosion of Conformity's home country is the United States. What genre of music are they known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9175_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9175_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the structured JSON format response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five files mention Corrosion of Conformity as a heavy metal band from Raleigh, North Carolina, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that Corrosion of Conformity is from Raleigh, North Carolina, USA. Therefore, the hometown of Corrosion of Conformity can be considered to be within the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Corrosion of Conformity is a band from Raleigh, North Carolina, United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Corrosion of Conformity is actually from Raleigh, North Carolina.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Corrosion of Conformity originated from Raleigh, North Carolina, United States, which makes their hometown Raleigh, North Carolina.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}